americansuperstarmag.com 2007-06-24

# Privacy | American Superstar Magazine™ | Celebrity News, Gossip, Interviews, Up-and-Coming Talent

[Sign up](http://www.americansuperstarmag.com/reg.php) for the _ASM_ Newsletter and get the latest celebrity news and gossip. You'll also be the first to know about the hottest up-and-coming actors, fashion designers, models, musicians and more. Plus, you'll receive special invites to our VIP events!

Do you have the talent to appear on American Superstar TV? Not everyone's video will make it past the judges since  
we only show the very best. 

[Submit](http://www.americansuperstar.tv/upload_videos.php) your video now and you could be starring soon!

Want to write about up-and-coming talent? Do you have a spin on celebrity life that you want to get off your chest?

We think everyone is capable of being a reporter at a cool entertainment pub. Email our publisher and include a writing sample if you have one.

**_Frank Sinatra_**

Frank Sinatra is an icon of American musical cool. His official career was singing: he began as a rail-thin crooner during World War II, and matured into the most respected pop singer of his generation. He also took up acting, winning an Academy Award in 1953 for his performance in _From Here To Eternity_. Along the way Sinatra developed a reputation as a well-dressed, fast-living, fist-fighting swinger, with a top-dog swagger that earned him the nickname "The Chairman of the Board." He was the acknowledged leader of the Hollywood 'Rat Pack' of the early 1960s, which included Dean Martin, Sammy Davis Jr. and others. Musically he was beloved as a stylish, heartfelt singer of old-school standards like _Come Fly With Me_ , _New York, New York_ , _All the Way_ and _Strangers in the Night_. He ranks with Bing Crosby, Elvis Presley and The Beatles as among the most influential pop musicians of the 20th century. 

| 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**  

American Superstar is dedicated to protecting your privacy and handling any personal information that we obtain from you with care and respect. We strive to deliver outstanding products, services and experiences. We value your support, and most importantly, your loyalty. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") is designed to answer your questions regarding our privacy policies and principles, and demonstrate our commitment to a strong and meaningful customer relationship.

**WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS**

  * This policy covers how American Superstar treats personal information that American Superstar collects and receives, including information related to your past use of American Superstar products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

  * This Site contains links to other Web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from our Site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**   

**_General_**

  * American Superstar collects personal information when you register with American Superstar, when you use American Superstar products or services, when you visit American Superstar pages or the pages of certain American Superstar partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. American Superstar may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, address, email address, zip code, phone number, birth date, gender, industry, work experience and personal interests. Once you register with American Superstar and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

  * If a user elects to use our Invite feature to invite a friend to our site, we ask them for the friend's email address. American Superstar will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the Site. American Superstar stores this email address for the purpose of sending reminders of the invitation. American Superstar does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. The friend may contact American Superstar to request the removal of this information from our database. 

  * American Superstar collects your credit card information if you purchase a product from the Site. Your credit card information is not collected or retained by American Superstar. It, along with the personal identifying information you submit, is transferred to and used by third party financial institutions to verify the credit card numbers and to authorize the processing of the transaction. Be sure to review all privacy policies published by our third-party service providers and contact them directly if you have questions as they may have privacy terms that differ from American Superstar's Privacy Policy. 

  * American Superstar automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, American Superstar cookie information, and the page you request. 

  * American Superstar uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**_Children_**

  * Children should always ask parents for permission before providing any personal information online. No information should be submitted to or posted on this Site by any Minor (a guest under 18 years of age) without the consent of a parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, we do not knowingly provide any personally identifying information about Minors, regardless of its source, to third parties, nor is this information knowingly used by American Superstar for any marketing or promotional purposes. 

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

  * American Superstar does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with American Superstar under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help American Superstar communicate with you about offers from American Superstar and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of American Superstar's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

    * We transfer information about you if American Superstar is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, American Superstar will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  * American Superstar displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, males ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

    * American Superstar does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

    * American Superstar advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks) and non-financial companies (such as stores, media, and entertainment companies).

  * American Superstar works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

**COOKIES**  

We may automatically track and collect your IP address, domain server, the type of computer and type of web browser you are using and use "cookies" to (i) customize content specific to your interests, (ii) ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and (iii) store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you use the Site. 

**_What are Cookies?_**

  * "Cookies" are pieces of electronic information (specifically, a string of text) that your browser and your operating system store on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. 

  * Cookies can store a user's ID and password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of previous selections or purchases. 

  * Cookies can enhance the user's visit. 

  * The use of cookies is an industry standard-you'll find they are used by most major commercial websites.

**_How We Issue and Use Cookies_**

  * We issue and use cookies to enhance your visit and the services we offer on the Site. The Site consists of thousands of pages of content. We want you to be able to find the information and offers that interest you, as quickly and easily as possible. The use of cookie technology helps us to achieve that objective. 

  * We issue and use cookies to keep track of the areas of the Site that interest our visitors most. In doing so, we can determine areas of the Site that are most popular and those that are not. Many improvements and updates to the Site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. 

  * Visitors to the Site who accept cookies may be presented with targeted messages, offers and ads on the Site and via email that we believe would be of value, based on observed preferences. 

  * If you have registered as a member of the Site and accept cookies, we can tailor your use to your personal preferences, and it is easier and faster to take advantage of the Site's benefits. 

  * If you have submitted your email address, you may receive targeted messages we believe you will find of value. Remember, you may request to be removed from your email subscription lists.

**_Your Choice to Accept or Deny Cookies_**

  * You can choose whether to accept or deny cookies; your browser on your computer is often initially set to accept cookies. However, you can choose to deny cookies and continue browsing the sites. 

  * Keep in mind that your choice to accept or deny a cookie is different from your choice to accept/deny email messages.

**YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES**

  * You can edit your American Superstar account, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 

  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the marketing preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 

  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the American Superstar service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and The American Superstar Newsletter, which are considered part of your American Superstar account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

  * You can delete your American Superstar account by visiting your account information page, by using an opt out message in an email, or by emailing the Site at [customerservice@americansuperstarmag.com](mailto:customerservice@americansuperstarmag.com) with your request.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

  * To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please contact us at [privacy@americansuperstarmag.com](mailto:privacy@americansuperstarmag.com).

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

  * American Superstar may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your American Superstar account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

  * Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [privacy@americansuperstarmag.com](mailto:privacy@americansuperstarmag.com).

**CONTACTING THE WEBSITE**

  * If you have questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at [privacy@americansuperstarmag.com](mailto:privacy@americansuperstarmag.com).

Effective Date: August 1, 2005 

|
